Just don't worry about it.
Okay.
Kobato.
Yes?
If you leave the window open like that, it doesn't matter how dumb you are, you're going to catch cold.
But I...
Come on, I'm cold.
Oh, I'm sorry!
It is still cold, isn't it.
Yeah, it's only February.
Now that you mention it, the convenience store had a bunch of magazines about chocolate.
Maybe having some chocolate will warm us up!
No, it's because Valentine's Day is coming up.
Valentine's Day?
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
... The Wanderers.
Fujimoto!
February 14th is Valentine's Day!
Yeah, and?
Let's have a Valentine's party at Yomogi!
Why at a nursery?
Don't they do that kind of thing?
Maybe somewhere else, but in Japan we just give chocolate.
Oh, yeah, I read that! So it'd work here too.
Just from the girls to the boys?
It's the day when girls give boys they like chocolate.
Is that what Valentine's is!?
Well, lately it's gone the other way too.
You really don't know much, do you.
To the boy they like...
What?
Let's give it a try!
Miss Sayaka's been worried about something again lately.
It's really hurting her, but she's trying not to show us that.
I think maybe we can cheer her up a little on Valentine's Day.
Ain't gonna work.
We don't even have the money for it.
It's okay!
I can find work at Tirol!
I'll go bother them tomorrow morning and get a job and earn enough for chocolate!
Calm down.
Okay...
So by making cake at Tirol, you're going to get the materials for everyone to make chocolates?
That's a pretty tall order.
Why, what's wrong with it?
Just for starters, working at Tirol is pretty tough.
They're there late every night.
That's why I can help out!
The boss said I can come after Yomogi lets out every day until Valentine's!
But...
It's okay!
I'll try my best to make Valentine's Day go well!
Rah, rah!
Okay. Do your best.
Kobato wants a Valentine's Day party here?
Yeah.
She's such a kind girl.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Good work.
Good work!
I can keep going!
I'd like to take you up on that, but it's closing time.
Wow, it's already that late?
Is there anything else I can help with?
There's only two days left until Valentine's Day.
You're working hard enough.
Want to go bring the sign in?
Sure, here I go!
I told you-
Looks like we landed somewhere weird again.
At least this time it wasn't over an ocean.
That almost killed us!
Ioryogi?
Look, it's a girl! There's humans here!
Hey! Things that look like a bun don't talk here!
Ioryogi!?
Er, no, he's named Kurogane...
Oh, and I'm Fai. This is Syaoran.
And this here is-
Huh?
What?
Oh, nothing.
That's it!
Mocona! You can talk now.
It won't surprise her.
Of course! Ioryogi's a talking stuffed animal too!
Ioryogi?
Dammit, Kobato, how long are you going to screw around!?
The boss is getting wo-
Ioryogi!
So this is Ioryogi!
I'm Mocona! Pleased to meet ya!
You're the one from that amusement park!
So you're wanderers?
Yeah.
Just four people?
Three people and one Mocona!
One Mocona?
That's how you count Moconas!
So that means that Ioryogi is one Ioryogi!
There damn well aren't two!
Wow, Kuro, Ioryogi, your voices really sound alike.
They don't!
They do!
Yeah, they do.
The Kurogane from this world is a tiny blue thing!
Shut up, bun!
So you're here on vacation?
Yeah.
I've read about going all sorts of places on vacation.
Have you decided where you're going?
No, not yet.
I wish we had somewhere to stay.
But...
We don't have any money from this world.
You don't have any money?
We can't use what we have.
Sounds tough.
We're all boys, so I guess we can just camp out.
I told you so.
How do we tell you're a guy? The color?
The cuteness.
Um... If you don't have anywhere to stay, why not stay at my place?
Saw that coming.
Bu... But...
It's okay! I have a whole room!
But there's only one mattress...
But we can all cozy up together!
But you're so tall...
I know, we can split up between the blanket and the mattress!
If you only have one mattress, does that mean you live alone?
No, I live with Ioryogi.
That makes it even worse.
It'll be fine! Really!
Let's take her up on it.
Umm...
I'm Hanato Kobato!
Happy to meet you, Kobato.
Hey, you guys.
No matter what happens, Ioryogi will protect you. Right, Kobato?
Hey...
All right, let's go to Kobato's!
Go!
Let's go!
Is this really a good idea?
He's gotta have something in mind.
Kuro, bro!
Do you know everything ?
Wait, wrong one!
Nope, he's just being a flake.
There's no school today, so I've gotta go straight to Tirol!
I couldn't sleep at all.
Kobato slept well.
Having people here doesn't change a thing for you, huh.
I'm sorry!
Um... I'm leaving now. Feel free to do whatever.
You're going to a cake shop, right?
Yeah! I help out there!
Let me guess, you'le looking for chocolates for Valentine's Day.
That's right!
Why don't you let us help too!
That's a great way to thank her for letting us stay!
It's that kind of shop, right?
Syaoran, why don't you go with her?
You're good at cooking.
Kuro wouldn't make a very good baker.
Wouldn't even try.
Kuro, let's look for other work, bro.
Get some cash.
And Mocona...
I'll hang out with Ioryogi!
Why!?
He looks like he'll make a great friend!
I have to go along with this!?
All right, that works.
Let's try our best!
Ioryogi, do your best!
We're buddies, let's play!
Who's your buddy!?
Don't let my cuteness carry you away!
Like I'd do that!
Who's that guy, Yui?
One of Kobato's friends.
I'm great at pretending I'm a stuffed animal!
Keep quiet!
Wow, that's great!
Syaoran, you're so good with your hands!
It just takes practice.
No matter how much I try, I can't get the wrapping right...
Don't try to do it all at once.
Do it bit by bit, like this.
Bit by bit...
I did it!
And quit singing!
Syaoran, you guys have been wandering for a while, right?
Yeah. But we're not going anywhere in particular.
Really?
We're traveling just to keep traveling.
So you don't have a destination?
It's hard to pick one.
We don't know how long we'll be able to stay in any given place.
But...
There's someone waiting for me.
Someone waiting for you?
She doesn't know when I'll be back, but she's still waiting.
I...
There's somewhere I want to go.
No matter what it takes.
It must mean something really special to you.
Or maybe there's someone there you want to be with.
Someone I want to be with...
The person I want to be with...
We worked hard!
You just sat there!
Yeah! I made a great mascot Mocona!
What's that supposed to mean!?
Welcome back!
How'd it go, bakers?
We're back! The boss was really impressed by how good with his hands Syaoran is!
Well, I...
They were really surprised by his clothes, too.
Oh, the clothes. We had problems with that too.
People kept asking if we were cosplaying.
Your joking about me looking like a cosplayer didn't help.
Here you go.
We only worked a day, so it's not much.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm happy to give it to you.
After all, you did put us up.
Thank you! I'll use it for Yomogi Nursery!
Already?
What's happening?
We have to go to the next world.
Whenever this earring glows...
Thanks for letting us stay.
It was only overnight, but it was fun!
Sorry to impose.
No, I'm sorry I couldn't do more for you.
Hey, Kobato's an-
Right?
But she doesn't seem very confident.
That's such a pretty light!
Yeah! I like it too!
People from other worlds can't do anything but watch over her.
Even us.
Take care of her.
You don't even have to tell me.
I hope you make it to where you want to go.
Thank you.
Those people were-
From another world.
There isn't just the human world.
There's also Heaven, Hell, and the Spirit Realm. Maybe more.
I hope Syaoran and the others make it to the one where people are waiting for them.
Valentine's Party
Let's try hard!
Everyone's having so much fen.
Yeah.
Kobato really worked hard on this.
Yeah... Yeah, she did.
Valentine's Party
Let's try hard!
What's that funny shape, Kobato?
What is it?
I wanted a star, but...
It looks like a starfish!
A starfish!?
She didn't just bring the chocolate, she also gave me some money.
She brought the boxes, wrapping paper, and cards, too.
I hope she's not working herself too hard...
Hey, Yoshio, who are you giving your chocolate to?
Mommy, Daddy, and my little sister!
I'm giving mine to Mommy, and then one to Kobato.
Thank you!
Valentine's Party
Let's try hard!
You've got to give the best chocolate to the person you like the best, right?
Kobato, who are you giving your best one to?
Me?
Let's try hard!
Wonder if Kobato's gonna remember to save any for me.
What do you want?
Kobato...
You're really running out of time.
In between the things I've lost
and the things I've been able to hold on to,
Your smile falls in that gap
It seems like I can reach it, but I can't
I can't fly
I just wanted to make you smile
My two wings weren't good enough
Why do I even have them?
Just smiling by your side
is all I can do.
Just warming you is good enough,
even though I want to embrace you
Even with these scarred, worthless wings,
right now I can smile
Next episode: "Spring's Pitter-patter."